{"questionsAndAnswers":[{"name":"Round 1","timeLimitInSeconds":100,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":100,"questions":[{"questionText":"How many snowdays did we have?","answers":[{"answerText":"One","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Three","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Two","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Four","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Is the world flat?","answers":[{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"It could be","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Who cares","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who played the grinch?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jim Curry","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Jim Curry","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I don't Know","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Tim Tebow","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Whats the 2nd number in pie?","answers":[{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Heres a free Bee","answers":[{"answerText":"Answer","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Answer","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Answer","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Answer","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which is not a movie?","answers":[{"answerText":"Star wars","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Dr. Grinch","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"The longest yar","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Grinch","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What was the name of the skeleton in the nightmare before christmas?","answers":[{"answerText":"Skully","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jack the ripper","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Sam","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jack The King","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What day is chirstmas?","answers":[{"answerText":"23rd","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"9th","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10th","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"25","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which is not usually played in a band?","answers":[{"answerText":"Bass","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Drums","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"CowBell","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Triangle","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which is heavier?","answers":[{"answerText":"Humans","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Elephants","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Mice","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hermit crabs","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which is faster?","answers":[{"answerText":"car","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"plane","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"boat","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"spaceCraft","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}